{
   "name":"quiz4",
   "que0":[
      {
         "question":"Ready to get started?",
         "options":{
            "A":"Yes",
            "B":"No"
         },
         "answer":"A"
      }
   ],
   "que1":[
      {
         "question":"What is the username of the accounts show in the video?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Russian Tutor",
            "b":"Skydestroyer",
            "c":"Michelangelo",
            "d":"In the Trend Probability Indicator channel"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que2":[
      {
         "question":"Why are we not learning about every feature that Facebook has?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Some tools don't work properly",
            "b":"We are only concerned with how to earn moneybags",
            "c":"There will be a second course to go over more features"
         },
         "answer":"b"
      },
      {
         "question":"What is the purpose of adding a username for your profile in the settings?",
         "options":{
            "a":"You never mentioned anything about usernames",
            "b":"It is a part of the account setup",
            "c":"So you can be tagged by other users and yourself in posts/comments"
         },
         "answer":"c"
      }
   ],
   "que3":[
      {
         "question":"**How do you answer all of the messages?**\n\n(replies, comments, DMs, etc)",
         "options":{
            "a":"All of your messages will be in your inbox and you can also leverage the chatbot with pre-determined questions and answers.",
            "b":"Expect to spend hours replying to potential clients there is no way around this",
            "c":"Hire a VA to reply to the messages"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      },
      {
         "question":"**Why are you connecting your Insta and Whatsapp to your Facebook?**",
         "options":{
            "a":"it unlocks special features for more followers",
            "b":"to cross-promote your Facebook for more exposure",
            "c":"Once you connect your Instagram, your Facebook feed will show you Instagram posts from people that you follow."
         },
         "answer":"b"
      }
   ],
   "que4":[
      {
         "question":"**What is the purpose of adding products to your page?**",
         "options":{
            "a":"To add passive income",
            "b":"Because you need to have your page filled with icons",
            "c":"We are setting up an E-Commerce site"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que5":[
      {
         "question":"**How many times should you post per day?**",
         "options":{
            "a":"1-2",
            "b":"2-3",
            "c":"3-4",
            "d":"4-6"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      },
      {
         "question":"**How should you maximize engagement when you are commenting on a post?**",
         "options":{
            "a":"Use one of the comments that Facebook suggests",
            "b":"Like, comment and DM each person that posts something in your niche",
            "c":"Follow the person (or join the group), like the post, leave a comment (with value), and comment under other people\u2019s comments (a thread)"
         },
         "answer":"c"
      }
   ],
   "que6":[
      {
         "question":"**Are you going to implement this course?**",
         "options":{
            "a":"Of course"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ]
}
